blissfullydomestic.com 2012-09-19

# Privacy Policy | | Blissfully DomesticBlissfully Domestic

## Commitment to Privacy

blissfullydomestic.com is owned and operated by Allison Worthington Media L.L.C. Your privacy is vastly important to us. We want you to have a safe and enjoyable time exploring our website.

In our effort to be completely transparent we have provided the following information to you. Because we gather certain types of information about our visitors, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or leave a comment on a post.

When registering on our site you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, and/or website url. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the ‘do we use cookies?’ section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

  * To determine which areas of our site you enjoy, based on traffic to those areas. (We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us to determine what information our readers enjoy the most.)

  * To improve your experience. (Non-personalized information such as your web request, referrer, browser type, or language helps us to better respond to your individual needs.)

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering a contest prize or service requested.

  * To send periodic emails (Occasionally if you leave a comment on a particular article, the author may respond to you via email to answer a questions or to thank you for providing your comment.)

The email address you provide will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your comment.

If you decide to opt-in to our newsletter mailing list, you will receive our email newsletter that provides a round up of the best posts, tips, and tutorials appearing on blissfullydomestic.com each week. Our newsletter may also feature paid third party advertising.

_Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email._

Subscriptions by email and feed readers for Blissfully Domestic are managed by our third party provider, Google Feedburner. For information on unsubscribing to Google Feedburner email subscriptions, please refer to the detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on April 4, 2009

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://blissfullydomestic.com

katie@blissfullydomestic.com
